themovechannel.com 2016-06-22

# TheMoveChannel.com | Privacy Policy | Website Data Usage

### Who we are

“We” are On The Move Limited trading as TheMoveChannel.com (The Move Channel) (company number 3997679) and our office address is 24 Jacks Place, Shoreditch, London, E1 6NN. 

We are registered for Data Protection under the Data Protection Act 1998 - Registration number Z4966058. VAT number GB 805 3650 46.

We are committed to protecting your privacy. This policy explains how and for what purposes we use the information collected about you via [www.TheMoveChannel.com](http://www.themovechannel.com/) or any sites operated by Us (referred to below as “this Site”). Please read this privacy policy carefully. By using this Site and any services we offer via this Site, you are agreeing to be bound by this policy in respect of the information collected about you via this Site. 

### Why Data is collected

Some of this Site can be accessed without submitting any data. However, there are times when we need to identify you by collecting personal information “Data” in order to enable the correct fulfilment of a particular Service.

Data is collected by this Site primarily in order to facilitate a range of Services that depend on personal information for their successful fulfilment. By using this Site you are deemed to have given consent for any personal details you have submitted to be used in the fulfilment of any such Services.

Such Services include making, managing and tracking enquiries you make regarding properties on this site, allowing you to manage your profile, email subscriptions and other personalisation settings, or using forms that can be pre-populated with your details to make them easier to use.

### What Data is collected

Data collected by us on this site, will be primarily that which is specifically required in order to facilitate any Service you have requested. From time to time, additional optional data may be collected for the purpose of building a profile of the users of this Site.

We will automatically gather other data “Statistics” such as your IP address, how you arrived at the Site, the kind of browser you are using, and statistics about how you use the Site. These Statistics will be used in aggregated form with current or potential advertisers to allow them to present their advertisements more effectively and for the purposes of improving how the Site works and to help us develop, administer and support the Site usage.

### Cookies

As part of offering and providing customisable and personalised services, this Site uses cookies to store and sometimes track information about you and to store your preferences.

A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. All areas on Site where you are prompted to log-in or that are customisable ask that you accept cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but if you prefer, you can edit your browser options to block them in the future.

In addition to the cookies we send to your computer some of our advertisers and third party ad servers will also send you their own cookies.

### How we will use this data

We will process your Data in the way indicated in this Privacy Policy. Over time the way we process your Data may change. We will let you know about changes that may not be obvious to you by publishing them in the Privacy Policy. By using the Site website you agree to any change we tell you about unless, within 60 days of that notice, you write and tell us not to handle your information in the new way.

Your Data may be used by us to contact you in writing, by telephone or by e-mail to offer you information, advertisements, products and services that we believe may be of interest to you. You can opt out of receiving any such contract at any time by amending your Data. 

We may also sell your data (or otherwise pass it on) to selected third parties who may use it to contact you by post, telephone, email, SMS or other reasonable method in relation to offers they feel might interest you, whether or not we enter into an agreement with you. In addition, we may disclose your personal information to a third party:

  * \- In the event we sell or buy any business or assets (in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such a business or assets)

  * \- If our business or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party (in which case personal data held about customers will be one of the transferred assets)

  * \- If we have a duty to disclose your personal data in order to comply with a legal request, or in order to enforce any of our terms and conditions

### Anti Spam Policy

Spam refers to unsolicited, bulk or indiscriminate messages, typically sent for a commercial purpose. TheMoveChannel.com has a zero-tolerance spam policy and is CAN-SPAM compliant.

TheMoveChannel.com works with email list partners to broadcast HTML newsletters that include one re more properties listed by its advertisers. Email list partners must not send unsolicited, bulk or indiscriminate messages, whether or not for a commercial purposes. 

In the unlikely event that you receive any message from TheMoveChannel.com or an email sent from an email list partner that references TheMoveChannel.com, please email the Data Protection Officer on antispam@themovechannel.com and the matter will be investigated.

### Amending your Data

You can use your password to view and edit your Data by clicking on the Services link near the top of the home page and then the various links within this section of the site.

### Access to the Data

We follow strict security procedures to ensure that your personal information is not damaged, destroyed, or disclosed to a third party without your permission and to prevent unauthorised access to it. The computers that store the information are kept in a secure facility with restricted physical access and we use secure firewalls and other measures to restrict electronic access.

You have a right to see a copy of the information we hold about you if you pay us the fee set by law. If you wish to see a copy of the information we hold about you please write to the Data Protection Officer, On The Move Ltd, 24 Jacks Place, Shoreditch, London, E1 6NN.
